Yuri Lima

Dublin, County Dublin, Ireland



y.m.lima19@gmail.com



+353834191605



linkedin.com/in/yuri-lima-40118bb3



https://www.yurilima.com.br/

Summary

I'm Brazilian living in Dublin. I've been coding in my spiring time for 10 years-ish. I started with C/C++ witch I'd done great projects. Then, I went to learn FreeRTO's witch I made Vending Machine. I've learned Python and Django Framework. I've made up my mind because I realized that I really love code and all things witch involves Computer Sciences and Technologies.

So, Very Welcome to my profile. Don't just take a look, go and scrutinize everything, enjoy.

Experience



Personal Board Blog and Professional Profile

Freelance, self-employed

Jan 2021 - Mar 2021 (3 months)

Please, Take a look at https://github.com/Yuri-Lima/Yuri-Lima

- << WebSite Yuri Lima >>
- 1. Personal Board Blog: I am building an application to show post from the hashtag. For while this is only a simple example because my real intentions are creating a new blog with a totally new propose. For more details about it, you can take a look at https://www.yurilima.com.br/blog. There you can follow week by week. Some new features are being added.
- 2. Professional Profile: For more details about it you can take a look at https://www.yurilima.com.br/ yurilima.

Number to Word - Translate Application

Freelance, self-employed

Sep 2020 - Dec 2021 (1 year 4 months)

Please, take a look at https://github.com/Yuri-Lima/NumbInWord

<< My first project in python >>

Translate numbers to words: (Goal)

The main idea of this project is in the future I will create a API.



RandomBox - Vending Machine

Freelance, self-employed

Nov 2016 - Apr 2017 (6 months)

Please take a look at https://github.com/Yuri-Lima/RandomBox_1

<< Integration: API + Loja Integrada + FreeRTO's + ESP32 >>

The main objective of the project has the intention of providing resources for Hardware developers, as well as providing access to the most diverse development platform options such as the module family of Espressif, Arduino, STM32, and various electronic components that every developer would like to have access to.

Homefi AX - Link House Automation

Freelance, self-employed

Apr 2015 - Sep 2016 (1 year 6 months)

Please take a look at https://github.com/Yuri-Lima/Link-House

<< Link House Automation >>

The project started in 2014. This project had the intention to created access for home automation to find a family income population.

The Homefi module was created to be easily installed by users with low knowledge of home electronics. The unique skills that required the user were the connection of wires for the system to be installed. The Homefi project was cancelled around at 2016 after the launch of the Chinese module called Sonoff. This module basically does the same service as Homefi AX. Web site: sonoff

CodeDominor - Educational Robot

Lapin Unifor

Feb 2018 - Dec 2019 (1 year 11 months)

Please, take a look at https://github.com/Yuri-Lima/CodeDomino_NewFirmwares

<< Code domino's for Decabot >>

Counter Water for Industry

Freelance, self-employed

Feb 2014 - Jun 2014 (5 months)

Please take a look at https://github.com/Yuri-Lima/AbacoCounter Kontus

<< Abaco_SE (Counter Machine) >>

Features:

- 1. Does not lose count if power is lost
- 2. Uses high-performance microcontroller
- 3. It even counts with translucent water bottles
- 4. Speed of up to 3 products per second
- 5. Dynamic Event Compensator (CES) avoids double counting on irregular objects
- 6. Number of digits automatically configured by the system
- 7. Internal clock is shown on the display
- 8. Easy to read in any quality and environment
- 9. Automatically resets the count the next day

Works without user intervention



General Coordinator

Gênio Azul

Apr 2017 - Apr 2019 (2 years 1 month)

Coordinate school unit (Team with more than 10 people), performing control activities and financial monitoring, cash flow, issuance of invoices, hiring professionals... Control and monitoring of teachers in their activities, creation and development of teaching materials, training of the commercial team and teachers. At certain times I was a teacher and substitute in case of absences... I have a good aptitude for the financial sector.

Software and Hardware developer to find new ways for kids to learn to code and improve their logic thinks.



Team Coordinator

Gráfica LCR

Nov 2016 - Apr 2017 (6 months)

- 1- Hardware developed in C/C++ to account for the development time of graphic materials such as outdoor arts, banners, layers.
- 2- Hardware developed in C/C++ to call clients that were waiting to get service.

Coordinate a team of 5 people, with goal establishments for input savings. Delivery of operational reports, to monitor industry metrics (Indicators). Financial control of cash flow, customer service. Quality control. Implementation of a management system.



Partner

Autocorerobotica

2014 - 2015 (2 years)

Free Time

I had E-commerce to sell electronics components, like Displays, Sensors, Gears, Motor, Board Prototypes Develop platform from Arduino and Spressif Company.

I had created too many technical videos on Youtube teaching how to get a code to run it and put it to work. as you can see on the link: https://www.youtube.com/c/AutoCoreRobotica/videos



Senior Coordinator

Banco Santander

Jun 2009 - Jun 2012 (3 years 1 month)

Main activities: Control of accounting standards; Management of cash flow in the treasury; Weekly meeting with cash battery to monitor monthly objectives; Customer service; Analysis of documents for account openings and card requests; Sales of banking products

Education



Universidade Estácio de Sá

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Business Administration and Management, General

2011 - 2015

Universidade de Fortaleza

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electrical and Electronics Engineering 2014 - 2016

Analyze problems and synthesize solutions by integrating interdisciplinary knowledge, elaborating projects and proposing economically competitive technical solutions and absorbing new technologies.

Licenses & Certifications

- 45th Internet of Things Seminar with NodeMCU, Telegram and Geniot Pro Industrial Microgenios
- NodeMCU ESP8266 Socket / Server Applications for IOT Microgenios
- FreeRTO's Real-Yime Operating System with ESP32 Microgenios
- CPA-10 ANBIMA
 Issued Jan 2010 Expires Jan 2015
 H7G6-E5R6-V1A1
- Programming Foundations: Object-Oriented Design LinkedIn
- in Learning REST APIs LinkedIn
- in HTTP Essential Training LinkedIn
- n Designing RESTful APIs LinkedIn

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • C (Programming Language) • Real-Time Operating Systems (RTOS) • Project Planning • Debugging • Hardware Architecture • Electronics • Social Media • Sensors • JSON